<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Adrien Skrzypczak</title>
        <link>//localhost:1313/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Adrien Skrzypczak</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Starting a personal blog</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2025/04/starting-a-personal-blog/</link>
            <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2025/04/starting-a-personal-blog/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/img/eye.webp&#34; alt=&#34;like tears in rain&#34; title=&#34;Like tears in rain&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here we are, I just decided to update my personal website. It was outdated and I needed a change, something new. I also wanted something more simple and minimalistic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But besides that, I have also learned a lot since then, and touched a lot of new topics. Sometimes I feel that this knowledge is hard to organize in my head, and I was trying to get an idea of how to organize it without just having notes and papers or files on my computer that I&amp;rsquo;ll probably never look at again.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/img/eye.webp" alt="like tears in rain" title="Like tears in rain"></p>
<p>Here we are, I just decided to update my personal website. It was outdated and I needed a change, something new. I also wanted something more simple and minimalistic.</p>
<p>But besides that, I have also learned a lot since then, and touched a lot of new topics. Sometimes I feel that this knowledge is hard to organize in my head, and I was trying to get an idea of how to organize it without just having notes and papers or files on my computer that I&rsquo;ll probably never look at again.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;ve always thought about writing articles and having a blog, but I didn&rsquo;t have the need at the time. Today I feel that this could be a great opportunity for me.</p>
<p>It could help me organize my notes and categorize all the topics I&rsquo;m learning and playing around with. Very good if future me needs to go back to something I struggled with or found interesting in the past!</p>
<p>It will help me learn and understand everything better. Don&rsquo;t we say, &ldquo;If you want to explain something to someone else, you have to understand it first&rdquo; ?
This is a chance to not only go over some topics, but to go a level deeper to get it into my head.</p>
<p>Of course, if this can be helpful to anyone out there, that would be a win.</p>
<p>If you, reader, are interested in my profile and want to learn more about me, this is also a chance to get a glimpse into my thought process and experiences.</p>
<p>For all these reasons, I think it is a good idea to document my work and career in this blog.</p>
<p>And maybe, all those moments will not be lost in time &hellip; like tears in rain.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
